brunel.net 2016-11-20

# Privacy statement - Technical staffing agency Brunel

It is Brunel’s policy to comply with data protection legislation. This legislation regulates the processing of information relating to you and grants you various rights in respect of your personal data. The privacy-sensitive information you send us is covered by this Privacy Statement. 

By clicking the “Accept” button during registration or by using this site, you explicitly accept, without limitation or qualification, of the collection, use and transfer of the personal information provided by you in the manner described in this Policy. 

This Statement is meant to inform you about the way we will use the personal details you provide through the website. This Statement is oriented towards job-seekers. Brunel treats privacy-sensitive information confidentially and will use the information exclusively for the purposes described below. The Site contains links to other web sites over which we have no control. Brunel is not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of other web sites to which you choose to link from this site. Brunel reserves the right to adjust this Statement in the case of changes in our policy, business operations, the law or jurisdiction gives occasion thereto. 

###  General Information 

We collect General Information of every visitor to the Brunel website. The General Information we collect includes information regarding how you use our site, the areas of our site that you visit, what services you access, and information about your computer hardware and software. In addition we gather numerical data and totals; the visitor’s identity is of no importance. We use the information we gather on the website for the purposes of providing our services, responding to any queries you may have, operating and improving the web site, fostering a positive user experience and delivering the products and services that we offer. 

###  Personal Information 

Personal Information is information that can be used to identify you. We do not collect personal information unless you choose to provide it to us. When you create a personal profile, Brunel will need some of your personal details, including your name and email address. We can use this information to provide our services which include providing you with information relating to your career experience and interests, to inform you about interesting job postings and other information you might find useful .We only do this if you indicate it is a service you want. The information we gather on the website may be shared within the Brunel group on a worldwide basis, including countries that might not have legislation that guarantees adequate protection with respect to your country of residence, in order to deliver these products and services. 

###  Responding to Job Postings 

We need a number of details from you before you can respond to job postings on our website. Although you personally decide which details you provide us, some details are mandatory. We use these details exclusively to bring you to our client’s attention and help you find a job as quickly as possible. 

By completing the registration form and/or applying for a job posting, you give Brunel your explicit permission to store this information in our database which will be accessible by our consultants world wide. Please be aware that the recipients of your data may potentially be located in any country in the world. If you are a resident in any EU member state, for example, you must be aware that the EU authorities do not generally consider that the regulations of non-EU countries ensure an adequate or equivalent level of protection as compared to the EU data protection regulations. 

### Changing and Deleting Details 

You are free to adjust your CV or change your account details at any time. You can also indicate at any time that you would like Brunel to delete your details. Please use the email address listed below to register your request, which Brunel will honour as quickly as possible. If you wish to revoke your consent to our Privacy Statement, please contact us at the e-mail address listed below. However, please note that if you do withdraw your consent, you may not be able to use the relevant services and your account and profile information will be deleted. 

###  Cookies 

Brunel uses cookies when carrying out its services. Cookies are small files that a browser saves to the hard disk to allow a website to recognise visitors. Cookies allow you to save your personal settings such as usernames, passwords and preferences. 

###  Security 

We at Brunel are committed to ensuring that the information you provided on our website is secure. We have therefore implemented appropriate technical and organizational measures to secure your personal data against loss and any form of unlawfully processing. We have put into place suitable physical, electronic and management procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect. 

###  Questions 

If you have any questions or comments about our privacy policy, please send an email to [info@brunel.net](mailto:info@brunel.net)
